https://www.barkers.co.nz/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We have put in place the following policy to protect your personal information. By using our website and/or providing information to us, you consent to the policy.
What personal information do we collect?
You may give us information about yourself, such as your name, address, email address and telephone numbers, when, for example, you become a customer, request our e-newsletter, request a catalogue or make a purchase from us. If you do not give this information, we may not be able to provide goods or services to you. When you visit our website we may collect more information, such as the address of your Internet service provider, the name of the web page directing you, and your clicks and activity on our site.
How do we use the personal information?
We may use the information to process your transactions, to administer your account, to conduct credit and other checks, for our own internal purposes (such as risk management, staff training and billing), to help us to develop our website to be more available and user friendly to our customers, and for any other use which you may authorise.
In addition, we may use the information to promote and market our products and services, or the products and services of others. However, we will not do this by email or text (except as part of an email which facilitates, completes or confirms a transaction with you) unless we have your express or deemed consent to do so. These emails and texts will always include an “unsubscribe” facility. Further, if you do not wish to receive them, you can update your records on our website, call us on 0800 BARKERS (0800 227537) or email us at fruit@barkers.co.nz.
Will we disclose the information to others?
We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.
However, we do use other companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf, such as delivering packages, sending mail and emails and processing payments. They will have access to your personal information needed to perform these services, but we will not authorise them to use your information for other purposes. In addition, we may provide statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site functions to reputable third parties.
Cookies
Our website uses a technology called cookies. A cookie is a small element of data that our website may send to your computer. Any such cookie is typically stored on your computer’s hard drive and permits our website to recognise you when you return. Our use of cookies helps us to provide you with a better experience during your use of our website by allowing us to understand what areas of the site are of interest to you. You may configure your web browser to not accept cookies, although you may experience a loss of functionality as a result.
Security
We take security seriously, and have taken steps to ensure your personal information is secure. We use secure servers, and industry standard data encryption whenever we are receiving or transferring your information online. However, we accept no responsibility for any loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration or destruction of personal information which you submit to us.
What about links to other websites?
Our website may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites have their own privacy policies, and we encourage you to review them. We have no responsibility for linked websites, and provide them solely for your information and convenience.
Updating your personal information
You may obtain confirmation from us as to whether or not we hold personal information about you. You may also request a copy of the information and/or request that corrections or changes are made to it. You can make changes to your personal information on our website, by calling us on 0800 BARKERS (0800 227537) or email us at fruit@barkers.co.nz.
Policy changes
We may change this policy from time to time and will notify you by posting an updated version on our website.
Feedback
We welcome your questions and comments about privacy at Barker’s. Please call us on 0800 BARKERS (0800 227537) or email us at fruit@barkers.co.nz.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle AJAX powered Gravity Forms.
$24.90 – Chutney and Ramekin Gift Box (Limited Time Offer)
